[
    {
        "question": "After she became Princess of Monaco in 1956, she used the bag to hide her growing belly while pregnant with her first child, Princess Caroline. That's the origin of the name of an Hermes bag named for what former actress?",
        "answer": ["Grace Kelly"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What technology company was founded in 1993 with the vision that the next wave of computing would be graphics-based? The company took its name from the Latin word for 'envy' and features product families GeForce, Quadro, and Tegra.",
        "answer": ["Nvidia"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Daniel Powter is a Canadian singer-songwriter that rose to fame as his song spent five weeks atop the Billboard charts in 2005. The song featured prominently in video montages of American Idol contestants who were eliminated from the show. What was Powter's two-word smash hit?",
        "answer": ["Bad Day"]
    },
    {
        "question": "A boy from 'The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle and Friends,' the namesake character of a certain 'Lagoon' comic strip, the battle-hardened World War II M4 tank, and the nutty scientist in 'The Klumps' all share what name?",
        "answer": ["Sherman"]
    }, 
    {   "question":"In logical argument and mathematical proof, a symbol consisting of three dots placed to form an upright triangle is used to represents which word?",
        "answer": ["Therefore"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "The world capital cities of Vienna, Bratislava, and Budapest all lie along what river, the second-longest in Europe?",
        "answer": ["Danube"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "The United Nations General Assembly adopted a historic document (Resolution 217) in Paris at its third session in 1948. The document is regularly abbreviated as UDHR, which stands for what?",
        "answer": ["Universal Declaration of Human Rights"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two months of the year are named for mortal men?",
        "answer": ["July", "August"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Who is the only singer to win the Grammy Awards for Album, Record, and Song of the Year twice? Both of the winning albums had titles that were two-digit numbers.",
        "answer": ["Adele"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the name for a type of rigid airship named for its German inventor that were first flown commercially in 1910 and carried tens of thousands of fare-paying passengers before World War I slowed down the airship business?",
        "answer": ["Zeppelin"]
    }, 
    {
        "question": "gjeoojger",
        "answer": ["eriojijoer"]
    }
]